{
  "1": {
  "questions": [
    { "question": "2 + 2 = ?", "answer": "4" },
    { "question": "Capital of India?", "answer": "delhi" },
    { "question": "5 * 3 = ?", "answer": "15" },
    { "question": "Binary of 4?", "answer": "100" }
  ],
  "hint": "Think logically",
  "clue": "Go where people are silent."
},
"2": {
  "questions": [
    { "question": "2 + 2 = ?", "answer": "4" },
    { "question": "Capital of India?", "answer": "delhi" },
    { "question": "5 * 3 = ?", "answer": "15" },
    { "question": "Binary of 4?", "answer": "100" }
  ],
  "hint": "Think logically",
  "clue": "Go where."
},
"3": {
  "questions": [
    { "question": "2 + 2 = ?", "answer": "4" },
    { "question": "Capital of India?", "answer": "delhi" },
    { "question": "5 * 3 = ?", "answer": "15" },
    { "question": "Binary of 4?", "answer": "100" }
  ],
  "hint": "Think logically",
  "clue": "Go"
}
}